for the that the bureaucracy is trying to arrest control of business away from the banks
through the postal savings bank and that's a bitter fierce conflict that may explode
the concord between japanese government and japanese business on which japanese
force for policy has been resting. And it's a very bitter contest and ruthless.
But in this country, we will have the question of, can we create either a new organ or make the
existing organs effective enough so that management have a boss, that they are accountable, but also
so that they are accountable for the performance of the enterprise, which in the long run is the
only thing that produces the golden eggs for anybody. We have a precedent in this country.
Every time you read in the paper that a company goes into chapter 11, we invoke our revision of
of the bankruptcy laws, 1896 and 1937,
which puts a preservation of the growing concern
before the interests of any one stakeholder.
And the creditors have not done badly under it.
In fact, if you compare what creditors got before it
with what they are getting now, they're
getting about four times as much.
When we forced government companies
into liquidation, which is the equivalent of the hostile
take over, creditors by and large never got more than $0.12 or $0.14 on the dollar.
That's what they get in a fire sale.
Now you can expect either 100% or 95% or what have you.
And so we have a precedent.
But whether we will be fast enough and wise enough and have enough vision to fashion the
next step in making the free enterprise something that is a social as well as an economic institution.
That's going to be the great challenge of the next 10 or 15 years, and we are beginning
to face up to it.
And Bill Goose promised you 220, but you all know old school teachers, they keep on talking.
So my apologies, but it's still only 2.25.
Thank you very much and thank you.